https://www.kelleybees.com/terms-and-conditions.html

Personal Protective Equipment
More...
Terms and Conditions
PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE. By using this site, you signify your agreement to these Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to these Terms and Conditions, do not use this site. The Kelley Beekeeping Company reserves the right to unilaterally modify these Terms and Conditions at any time.
Restrictions on Use of Materials
This site is copyright protected. Any textual or graphic material you copy, print, or download is licensed to you by Kelley Beekeeping Company for your personal, non-commercial home use only, provided that you do not change or delete any copyright, trademark or other proprietary notices.
If you download software from the site, the software, including all files and images, contained in or generated by the software, and accompanying data (together referred to as "Software") are deemed to be licensed to you by Kelley Beekeeping Company, for your personal, non-commercial home use only. Kelley Beekeeping Company does not transfer either the title or the intellectual property rights to the Software and Kelley Beekeeping Company retains full and complete title to the Software as well as all intellectual property rights therein. You may not sell, redistribute or reproduce the Software, nor may you decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble or otherwise convert the Software to a human-perceivable form. All trademarks and logos are owned by Kelley Beekeeping Company or its licensors and you may not copy or use them in any manner.
This site is controlled and operated by Kelley Beekeeping Company from its office within the State of Kentucky, United States of America. Kelley Beekeeping Company makes no representation that materials in the site are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who choose to access this site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable. Software from this site is subject to U.S. export controls. No software from this site may be downloaded or otherwise exported or re-exported into (or to a national or resident of) Cuba, Iraq, Libya, North Korea, Iran, Syria or any other country to which the U.S. has embargoed goods or to anyone on the U.S. Treasury Department's list of Specially Designated National or the U.S. Commerce Department's Table of Deny Orders. By downloading or using the software, you represent and warrant that you are not located in, under the control of, or a national or resident of any such country or on any such list.
Disclaimers and Limitation of Liability; Forward-Looking Statements
Kelley Beekeeping Company may change, move or delete portions of, or may add to, this web site from time to time.
THE MATERIALS IN THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. KELLEY BEEKEEPING COMPANY DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OR THE RESULTS OF THE USE OF THE CONTENT OR OTHER MATERIALS IN THIS SITE IN TERMS OF THEIR CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE.
TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSABLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, KELLEY BEEKEEPING COMPANY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. KELLEY BEEKEEPING COMPANY DOES NOT WARRANT THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS OR USEFULNESS OF ANY INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THIS SITE. KELLEY BEEKEEPING COMPANY DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE MATERIALS AVAILABLE ON THIS SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THE MATERIALS, THIS SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES THEM AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. YOU (AND NOT KELLEY BEEKEEPING COMPANY) ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR AND CORRECTION.
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, NEGLIGENCE, SHALL KELLEY BEEKEEPING COMPANY BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM THE USE OF, OR THE INABILITY TO USE, SITE OR ANY DOWNLOADED MATERIALS, EVEN IF KELLEY BEEKEEPING COMPANY OR ITS REPRESENTATIVE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IN NO EVENT SHALL KELLEY BEEKEEPING COMPANY'S TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FROM ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES, AND CAUSES OF ACTION (WHETHER IN CONTRACT, OR OTHERWISE) EXCEED THE AMOUNT YOU PAID TO KELLEY BEEKEEPING COMPANY, IF ANY, FOR PRODUCTS PURCHASED ON THIS SITE.
APPLICABLE LAW MAY NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, OR THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Links to Other Web Sites
Kelley Beekeeping Company makes no representation whatsoever regarding the content of any other web sites which you may access from this site. When you access a non-Kelley Beekeeping Company web site, please understand that it is independent from Kelley Beekeeping Company and that Kelley Beekeeping Company has no control over the content on that web site. A link to a non-Kelley Beekeeping Company web site does not mean that Kelley Beekeeping Company endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content or use of such web site.
Submissions
Should any viewer of a document on this web site respond to Kelley Beekeeping Company with information including feedback data, such as questions, comments, suggestions, or the like regarding the site, or the content of any item, such information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Kelley Beekeeping Company shall have no obligation of any kind with respect to such information. In addition, Kelley Beekeeping Company shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, display, exhibit, transmit, perform, create derivative works, and distribute the information to others without limitation, and to authorize others to do the same. Further, Kelley Beekeeping Company shall be free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such information for any purpose whatsoever, including, but not limited to, developing, manufacturing and marketing products and other items incorporating such information. This paragraph is not intended to apply to any personal information about you (such as name, mailing address and e-mail address), the use of which will be governed by Kelley Beekeeping Company's Privacy Policy.
In consideration of Kelley Beekeeping Company's continuing efforts to enhance and improve these products and to respond to feedback from users, you agree to transfer such ideas, concepts, know-how and techniques to Kelley Beekeeping Company without any compensation. You agree to execute any and all documents that Kelley Beekeeping Company may reasonably request in connection with confirming Kelley Beekeeping Company's ownership of and unlimited right to use such ideas, concepts, know-how and techniques.
You are solely responsible for the content of any comments you make. You agree that no comments submitted by you to this web site will: (i) violate any right of any third party, including copyright, trademark, privacy or other personal or proprietary rights; (ii) be or contain libelous or otherwise unlawful, abusive, or obscene material or constitute the misappropriation of the trade secrets of any third party; and (iii) disparage the products or services of any third party. You agree not to submit any personal information (other than your email address or user name) through email sent to other users or messages posted on this site by you.
Termination
This Agreement is effective unless and until terminated by either you or Kelley Beekeeping Company. You may terminate this Agreement at any time by no longer using this web site, provided that all prior uses of this web site shall be governed by this Agreement. Kelley Beekeeping Company may terminate this Agreement at any time and without notice, and accordingly deny you access to this web site, in Kelley Beekeeping Company's sole discretion for any reason, including your failure to comply with any term or provision of this Agreement. Upon any termination of this Agreement by either you or Kelley Beekeeping Company, you must promptly destroy all materials downloaded or otherwise obtained from this web site, as well as all copies of such materials, whether made under the terms of this Agreement or otherwise.
Click here to see Kelley Beekeeping Company's Privacy Policy.
Who We Are News and Events Beekeeping Education Customer Support FAQ's Retail Store Terms and Conditions Privacy Policy
BeeFriend Us
Sign up for our newsletter.
Sign up to receive coupons, discounts and product updates.
Bee Social
Stay connected to Kelley Beekeeping
© 2020 Kelley Beekeeping
Merchant Services
